Here we have a struct declaration for a rectangle.
这里我们有一个矩形的结构声明。
When you declare a struct, the struct tag, in this case rect_tag,
当你声明一个结构时，结构标签（在本例中为 rect_tag）会
identifies the struct's type.
标识该结构的类型。
But by itself is not a type name.
但其本身并不是一个类型名称。
When you want to name the struct type, you have to include the struct keyword,
当你想命名结构类型时，你必须包含 struct 关键字，
like you see here.
就像你在这里看到的那样。
Many programmers find it tedious to right struct everywhere they need to use fixed
许多程序员发现，在需要使用固定结构
struct types so they use typedef to define a new type name for the struct type.
类型的任何地方修改 struct 都很乏味，因此他们使用 typedef 为结构类型定义新的类型名称。
One way to use typedef with our rectangle struct is shown here.
这里显示了在我们的矩形结构中使用 typedef 的一种方法。
The typedef keywords says that we are going to make a new name for
typedef 关键字表示我们将为
an existing type.
现有类型创建一个新名称。
The new name in this case rect_t comes last in the declaration and
在本例中，rect_t 的新名称在声明中排在最后
the name of the existing type comes between them.
，现有类型的名称介于它们之间。
Notice that here the existing type is struct rect_tag.
请注意，这里的现有类型是 struct rect_tag。
Now we can just use rect_t as a type name.
现在我们可以使用 rect_t 作为类型名称了。
It is an alias or another name for struct rect_tag.
它是 struct rect_tag 的别名或其他名称。
There are a couple of other ways we can do the same thing with typedef.
我们还有其他几种方法可以用 typedef 做同样的事情。
We mention them all so that if you see one or
我们都提到了它们，这样如果你
the other ways in someone else's code, you will not be confused.
在别人的代码中看到一种或另一种方式，你就不会感到困惑。
We can combine the struct declaration and typedef into one statement.
我们可以将 struct 声明和 typedef 合并为一个语句。
This follows the same rules we just discussed.
这遵循的规则与我们刚才讨论的规则相同。
The new name rect_t goes at the end of the typedef statement.
新名称 rect_t 出现在 typedef 语句的末尾。
And the existing type goes between the new name and the typedef keyword.
而现有类型介于新名称和 typedef 关键字之间。
It just happens that here the existing type gets declared
碰巧这里的现有类型是在
in the typedef statement.
typedef 语句中声明的。
The third option is the same as the previous one,
第三个选项与前一个选项相同
except that the struct tag is omitted.
，只是省略了 struct 标签。
This makes a struct with no tag and immediately aliases this struct to rect_t.
这将生成一个没有标签的结构，并立即将该结构别名为 rect_t。T
Typedef has uses beyond just structs.
ypedef 的用途不仅仅是结构。
Sometimes, we are writing some code that deals with RGB values for pixels.
有时，我们正在编写一些处理像素的 RGB 值的代码。
In this hypothetical example, we initially use unsigned ints to represent the red,
在这个假设的示例中，我们最初使用无符号整数来表示每个像素的红
green, or blue components of each pixel.
色、绿色或蓝色分量。
But what happens if later we realize that it would be better to use an unsigned char
但是，如果稍后我们意识到最好使用无符号字符，
since RGB values can only be between 0 and 255 and we don't want to waste memory.
因为RGB值只能在0到255之间，而且我们不想浪费内存，会发生什么。
With the way we wrote the code, we have to go find every single
按照我们编写代码的方式，我们必须找到
place that we used unsigned int to represent an RGB value and change it.
我们使用无符号整数来表示 RGB 值的每个位置并对其进行更改。
We can't even use the search and replace functionality of our editor
我们甚至无法使用编辑器的搜索和替换功能，
since there may be other uses of unsigned int that do not represent RGB values.
因为可能还有其他用法 unsigned int 不代表 RGB 值。
So we don't want to change them.
因此，我们不想更改它们。
Such a change is tedious and error-prone.
这样的更改既乏味又容易出错。
In fact, one important rule of programming is to write code so
实际上，编程的一个重要规则是编写代码
that if you have to change something, you only have to change it in one place.
，这样，如果您必须更改某些内容，则只需在一个地方进行更改即可。
Now suppose we had originally written our code this way.
现在假设我们最初是用这种方式编写代码的。
Here we used typedef to make rgb_t an alias for unsigned int.
在这里，我们使用 typedef 将 rgb_t 设为无符号整数的别名。
pip value.
然后在我们需要谈论 RGB 点值的所有地方都使用 rgb_t 作为类型名称。
With this code, if we want to change the type we use for RGB values,
有了这段代码，如果我们想更改我们用于 RGB 值的类型，
we can just change the typedef statement and everything else will change correctly.
我们只需更改 typedef 语句，其他所有内容都会正确更改。
As a side benefit, this helps the readability of our code.
附带的好处是，这有助于提高我们代码的可读性。
Anyone reading the code can tell when a variable, parameter, or
任何阅读代码的人都可以分辨出变量、参数或
return value is an RGB value since its type is rgb_t.
返回值何时是 RGB 值，因为它的类型是 rgb_t。T
Typedef can be great to make your code easier to modify and easier to read.
ypedef 非常适合让你的代码更易于修改和阅读。